This was a cauldron once, but the wild got in.
And now the enemy too.
[Cultist]
Should listen to orders.
If you don't know what it is, then be damn sure to leave it alone.
Calm.
[Cultist]
This will not go well for you.
See her up there!
Must have been a cave in, a big one.
[Cultist]
Tired, but I will endure. For shadow, for Meridian.
She's up on high!
[Cultist]
…down, we're not out!
Look, up there!
Can breathe again.
Haven't you got anything better to do?
[Cultist]
Get them!
Where did she go?
[Cultist]
Here!
I'm not here.
[Cultist]
Cancel the search, I got her!
Don't stop looki… aah!
Full already.
[Cultist]
Don't get too close to that thing, that's an order.
Let's see what they're so afraid of.
No room.
That's it, more machines I can override.
[Cultist]
What have you done?
Cut her down!
[Cultist]
Get over here, she's coming!
Die, apostate!
[Cultists]
- Look out! She has unleashed machines!
- Fear the power of…
Machines must've been stored here.
[Cultist]
The Shadow gives you strength, use it!
Down you go!
Got too much already.
Can't be too prepared.
[Cultist]
Stalkers!
Ha ha, I dropped it!
I'd have to ditch something.
[Cultist]
Please, don't let it see me.
Shadow guide me!
Calm, calm.
Move along now.
[Cultist]
The Sun can't save you now!
Can't carry more.
Now they're hunting me.
[Cultist]
Don't lose her.
Off you go.
Now's my chance!
I can get out of this.
My turn.
Almost out of here.
Still sniffing around.
These aren't cheap.
[Cultist]
Cancel the search, I got her.
Gotta be around here, somewhere.
Look at this!
[Cultist]
Help me…
Survive this.
Well, so much for their salvage operation.
They meddled with something they couldn't control.
Like they did with me.
[Cultist]
Take them down!
Something above us.
Heavy. It's hard, too.
That's coming with me.
I can't spare the weight.